Cascarr Ihesie

9th floor Diamond Flower Building• Hanoi, VN 10000 • +84 (034) 2788-713 • c.ihesie91@gmail.com

DEVELOPER

A strong desire to keep learning and working with a variety of technologies

Positive and proactive solution-driven professional, courageous in excelling in a highly collaborative work environment, finding solutions to challenges and focused on client satisfaction. Proven experience developing client-focused web apps using solid JavaScript and PHP programming language, HTML5 and CSS with strong understanding of web browser ecosystem. Responding to challenges by designing and developing solutions and building web applications aligned to client's services while paying strong attention to details and applying a strong sense of curiosity. Translating solutions into code and working across many different APIs, third-party integrations and databases using a strong googling and IT literacy skills set. Great team player who isn't afraid to ask questions when necessary. A progressive learner keen on skills improvement, and possesses a solid understanding of client-relations using great written and spoken English skills.

Key skills include:

- JavaScript
- HTML5
- CSS

- PHP
- MongoDB
- SQL relational databases

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCES

ECOMMERCE ARCHITECT - [2021 - current]

Designing / Development and Deployment of e-Commerce Systems at Cletrav. Co, Hanoi.

SOFTWARE ENGINEER - [2021 - current]

Working alongside UI Engineers to Design and Manage Interfaces for Web Games at Glis Games.

PHASER 3 SOFTWARE ENGINEER (INTERN) - 2020

• Learning HTML5 Game Development for Cross-Platforms at Glis Games.

JUNIOR PHP PROGRAMMER (INTERN) - 2017

• Learning and Working with Teammates to Develop Server-Side Applications using Laravel Framework at Scuti.co, Hanoi, Vietnam.

ELEMENTARY SCHOOL TEACHER - [2018 - 2020]

Teaching and Working with Young Learners.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

UNIVERSITY of GREENWICH, London, UK.

B.Sc. (Hons) in Computing, 2018.

FPT UNIVERSITY, Hanoi, Vietnam.

Higher Diploma (HD.SE) in Software Engineering, 2015.